[OVERDO]
[Episode 30]
[Li Residence]
Li Boze?
Li Boze!
Boze.
The Zhang family
was behind
the North-South Railway bombing case
19 years ago.
Although Marshal Li
participated in the plan at the time,
both sides agreed
to only target Murong Feng
and seize control.
[Nancheng Station]
However, it triggered a massive explosion,
killing and injuring
hundreds of civilians.
This became a knot in the Marshal's heart.
Afterwards,
the reason given by the Zhang family
was that nearby explosives
were accidentally ignited.
It was an accident.
But looking back now,
the Zhang family was already backed by
the Chamber of Commerce back then.
Their purpose was
to sabotage cooperation efforts.
Also,
Master Fang's death 7 years ago
was caused by the Zhang family
and the Chamber of Commerce.
Initially, the Chamber of Commerce
wanted to conduct
Red Pill experiments in Nanyang.
That batch of medicine
was secretly transported
by the Fang family's fleet.
To protect the civilians on shore,
Master Fang sank the ship
and killed himself.
The Red Pill plan
was forcefully delayed for 7 years.
It means that the raw materials
for this medicine
are not that easy to find.
The Marshal said that
if getting rid of this batch of Red Pills
could delay progress by another 7 years,
it'd have been worth it.
Boze,
the Marshal asked me
to pass a message to you.
The Marshal said,
"Li Boze,
a real man should die like me.
Don't make me look down on you."
Is there anything else?
Boze.
Ganging up to lie to me, huh?
Fine.
Boze.
You guys have been lying to me all along.
Every single
one of you
is a liar who abandoned me.
When I wanted to be a good police officer,
you lied to me
and told me to guard this home.
When I wanted to guard this home,
you started
talking to me about the greater good.
Was it not you guys
who preached it all to me?
But in the end?
Everything became my fault.
I became the sinner
who showed no consideration.
Let me tell you all right now!
I!
Will walk down this path
to the very end.
I'm going to tell all of you that
you are
all wrong!
Out of my way.
Boze!
Young Master Qingyi.
Let me go.
Li Boze.
Li Boze!
This is your home.
Where are you going?
Home?
Does this home
still have my family?
You still have me.
It's been 7 years.
I've waited 7 years for you.
I was waiting for you to tell me
you'd let go of your prejudice
against my father,
and that you still had me
in your heart!
But why are you saying it now?
Is it out of regret?
Hai Tangqing.
Or is it out of pity?
I admit it.
Li Rongzhang wasn't a heinous villain.
But I wasn't wrong to hate him.
Yes, you've been waiting all these years.
But did you think I had it easy?
Yes, you're right.
Your brother is dead.
And my father is dead too.
We are
even now.
Li Boze!
When did I ever
truly belong to this family?
This tree
was planted by my father
when Qingyi was a child.
After Qingyi left,
Father would often stand
under the tree and miss him.
I always thought I'd have a chance
to ask him
when and why
he planted this tree.
But now,
those unspoken words
can never be brought up again.
Boss Hai.
Our unspoken feelings
need not be brought up again either.
[Lanxin Theater]
Luckily, you were just hit by debris.
Otherwise, you'd have gotten
more than just a scratch.
It's nothing.
Good thing I was at the station today.
Otherwise,
Li Boze might not have survived either.
Boze
always wanted a complete family.
But now,
everything that gave him
a sense of security and love
is all gone.
I can't even imagine
how sad he must be.
He had warmth.
But what about you?
When I was little,
I fantasized endlessly about
Li Rongzhang's death.
But today,
I didn't even dare
to see his body.
This man
was a violent father on one hand,
and a martyr for his nation on the other.
His ambition led to mistakes,
but he stepped up when he realized them.
Looking back now,
maybe we never truly understood him.
So I don't know
whether I should laugh
or cry.
Do you think
Li Rongzhang ever regretted
how he treated me
and my adoptive mother
in the last moments of his life?
Get some good sleep.
Maybe he'll tell you in your dream.
I hope it's not a nightmare.
What game is this?
What is this?
What game, you ask?
A horse-carry.
Is it high?
Is it?
Yes.
When you grow up,
you can ride a real horse.
Okay?
Okay.
Daddy will buy you a horse to ride.
Okay?
Ride a horse into battle.
Join the battlefield,
okay?
Okay.
Mommy is here.
Make room for Mommy.
Sit over here.
Hold it carefully.
-Be careful.
-Give it a hug.
So nice.
Look at its little nose.
Pet it.
Give a hug.
So nice.
We noticed it early this morning.
In just one morning,
he started becoming delirious.
The disease progresses extremely fast.
At first,
we thought it was just a fever
caused by a wound infection,
but all common medicines
are useless on him.
What's worse,
other students in the aviation school
have started showing the same symptoms.
They are exactly the same
as the symptoms Mr. Bao described.
Lock down the school.
From now on,
no one is allowed in or out.
Yes.
Here, spray more here.
Here, sprinkle more here.
Don't miss this spot.
And here,
watch it.
[Regulations for the Use
and Transportation of RDX Explosives]
Wasn't this batch of Red Pills
already destroyed?
Why are there still infection symptoms?
Could there be some left behind?
Impossible.
The aviation school students
couldn't have used the Red Pills.
This batch of infections
was not spread through the Red Pills.
Did you ask
what else the students
have been in contact with?
We have already tested
all possible sources of infection.
It must be due to either
oral medicine,
food,
water sources, or...
Come in.
Principal,
the test results are out.
It's the water tank.
The water storage tank
of the aviation school
has an excessive dose of unknown bacteria.
Got it.
You may leave.
Water tank?
The entire school
uses this water tank.
Who knows how many teachers
and students are infected?
This thing has an incubation period.
Right now,
it has only just begun.
What's Zhang Mingshu thinking?
How dare he poison the military camp?
I heard that at the aviation school,
students are also getting sick.
It seems the Zhang family
wants to use bacteria
to wipe out
the military's effective strength
and then control Nancheng.
Lock down the military camp.
Screen all patients with symptoms
and isolate them separately.
Commander Tang.
Liu Zhou.
From now on,
including myself,
everyone
is forbidden to leave the military camp.
Yes.
I have sent a message
to Murong Qingyi and Li Boze.
There is only one antidote.
Whoever cooperates with
the East Asia Chamber of Commerce first
will get the antidote.
As for the other party,
our hands are tied.
The bait has been dropped.
The angler
just needs to wait patiently
for the fish to bite.
This way,
we can completely drive a wedge
between Murong Qingyi and Li Boze,
and also weaken the forces
of the Ying Army and the aviation school.
A brilliant move, Chairman.
At first, I thought that kid
from the Murong family
was highly capable.
But even now, he doesn't know
that the
addictive Red Pills sold in the market
are nothing but
crudely made opium.
Making opium into the shape of red pills.
Chairman, your little trick
has completely fooled them.
Little do they know that
only the batch sent to the train station
is the real deadly weapon.
It can be secretly
mixed with regular Red Pills
and enter the market.
Seven years ago,
that batch of disease-causing Red Pills
was completely destroyed by Fang Youshen.
It took us a lot of effort
to develop the new batch.
But before it even left the train station,
it was blown to pieces
by that old bastard,
Li Rongzhang.
Now,
we can only use the remaining
original reagents.
One gram of this
is equivalent to
hundreds of pounds
of the previous Red Pills.
The original reagent is unstable
and sensitive to high temperatures.
It must be transported
and stored properly.
This time,
we can't afford any more mistakes.
Rest assured, Chairman.
Nothing will go wrong this time.
Patients initially develop
fever and blisters,
accompanied by local wound ulceration.
At this stage,
there is a risk of infection
through mucosal
and blood contact.
Fortunately, it's controllable.
Ensure you disinfect
after contacting patients.
Their wounds
will gradually become
unbearably itchy and painful.
Patients will inevitably
struggle and scratch,
which hinders scabbing.
At this stage,
the patients' consciousness
will alternate between
confusion and lucidity.
The longer the disease progresses,
the longer
the periods of confusion will last,
until death.
Currently,
we have no effective drugs to control it.
We can only isolate them
and reduce their temperature.
As long as body temperature
is well controlled,
it can shorten
the duration of the onset.
Whether they survive
depends on their physical condition.
Come hold him down!
Hurry!
Hurry.
Isolate all the patients!
All items used by the patients
must be taken away!
Take these clothes and bedsheets
away for disinfection!
All blood-stained clothes
must be destroyed!
This patient's temperature
has finally dropped.
His temperature
hasn't dropped for over half an hour.
We need someone here for
physical cooling immediately.
Okay.
Let's go.
It hurts.
It's itchy.
I'm so itchy.
Young Marshal.
You haven't eaten for days.
Have something to eat first.
Thank you.
By the way.
Today,
how many new patients were admitted?
Twenty-three cases.
It's so itchy.
Is this the limit?
Pardon? I didn't catch that.
I said,
there will only be more and more patients.
We'll be busy for a long while.
-Go to bed early.
-It itches.
It's itchy.
When a patient's coma
exceeds 45 minutes,
he reaches a critical point.
If the fever is not reduced in time,
he will very likely
never wake up again.
Bury him properly.
This is the first death.
It's only been 8 short days.
In these 8 days,
you haven't wasted even a second.
We figured out the course of
this strange disease so quickly
thanks to you.
Don't be so hard on yourself,
Qingyi.
I was the one who rejected Zhang Mingshu.
But the price was paid
by the innocent students
of the aviation school.
I don't care about myself,
but I have no right
to make decisions for them.
I met someone today.
It was quite the coincidence.
Guess who?
Back in the Huo family's vault,
among the girls
who fought their way out with us,
there was one named Zhaodi.
Ms. Ye changed her name.
Encouraged by Ms. Ye,
she got into the aviation school.
She wasn't infected,
but she was badly frightened.
Yet she still refuses to leave here.
She said her father sold her
to the Huo family,
and she almost died there.
Getting into the aviation school
is something she'll never regret.
She also asked me to tell you that
she thinks you did the right thing.
Even if we die,
we will never betray our country.
Thank you.
I'm fine, don't worry.
Go back first.
I want to be alone for a while.
Rest early.
Everything in the aviation school
still depends on you.
Don't worry.
[Isolation Room]
Good work.
Where is the principal?
Oh, yeah.
The principal usually stays here all day.
I haven't seen him today either.
Dr. Lin,
prepare another isolation room.
If the first batch of sick students
shows improvement,
transfer them immediately.
They must be separated
from the severe cases.
We don't know how long
this incident will last.
Ms. Ye,
supplies in the aviation school
must be provided uniformly
and allocated to the patients first.
Rest assured.
Even if the principal is not here,
the aviation school cannot be in chaos.
[Isolation Room]
[5:30 p.m.]
[5:30 p.m: Felt a foreign object
in my throat]
Qingyi.
Open the door, Qingyi.
I know you're in there.
I'm fine.
Go back to your work.
Don't try to lie to me.
Are you infected too?
Open the door!
I told you I'm fine. Leave now!
You have a fever.
How can you control your
temperature by yourself in here?
You'll die faster
if you coop yourself up here.
Listen to me.
If they find out
that I'm infected,
it will shake their morale.
If I really get sick,
you must lock me up.
You absolutely cannot let anyone know.
Day 2 since Qingyi's illness.
He started losing consciousness.
The number of deaths in the school
keeps increasing.
No one knows
who will be next.
♪ I happened to ♪
♪ Hear your name ♪
Snow fell before the
beginning of Winter,
♪ And all the memories ♪
hinting that this year's winter
♪ Came flooding back ♪
would be very long.
♪ There I stood in the falling snow ♪
Yet I secretly rejoiced
at the snow's arrival.
♪ Wrapped in my coat ♪
♪ My heart pounding ♪
Day 4 since Qingyi's illness.
♪ Walking down that old road ♪
His coma lasted for half an hour.
♪ Stopping every few steps ♪
♪ In the misty train car ♪
Every time he lost consciousness,
♪ I wish I could ask you once more ♪
I didn't know if he would wake up.
♪ If you have any ♪
♪ New corny jokes to tell ♪
Qingyi!
I heard from Ms. Ye that
♪ Memories are like falling into a trap ♪
some students survived the onset phase
♪ Full of mud ♪
and their temperatures returned to normal.
♪ The more I struggle,
the more suffocated I become ♪
I've never prayed for anything.
♪ But I couldn't resist collecting them ♪
But at this moment,
♪ I keep collecting ♪
I hope such good luck
♪ Every word and comment ♪
can fall upon Qingyi too.
♪ They speak of you ♪
♪ You are so clear ♪
♪ So close and so clear ♪
♪ If you possibly ♪
♪ Still have the courage ♪
♪ Then take me away from here ♪
♪ Please stop doubting ♪
♪ My determination to run away with you ♪
Qingyi.
You haven't eaten all day.
I won't eat. Leave now.
Here.
You can't sleep.
You can't sleep!
If the coma exceeds 45 minutes...
Murong Qingyi.
You finally have a family.
Li Rongzhang.
A general's success
is built on a thousand skulls,
don't you understand?
You must hold on.
I said,
I only want Murong Feng's life.
Open the door.
Open the door!
Hurry!
Kid,
trying to tip off the Murong family?
You're courting death.
Assassination?
Why should I believe you?
You can't even speak coherently.
Who wants to kill your father?
Where?
Tell me.
I don't know.
It hurts...
Mother,
please believe me.
don't go...
Qingyi!
Your temperature has gone down.
We made it through.
We will be fine now.